shiprocket.co 2016-03-25

# Privacy Policy | ShipRocket.in

### ShipRocket Privacy Policy

ShipRocketTM collects e-mail addresses and other contact details of people who register at our website and send us e-mail. The information we collect is not shared with or sold to others except under the certain circumstances and which your use of the Service is deemed to provide to us a valid consent to disclose the following: In order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ShipRocket’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We share information about our Members with third parties, such as advertisers or partners, for marketing and promotional purposes. However, except as otherwise ShipRocket does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other companies. ShipRocket uses your information on a cumulative basis to help operate our web sites and enhance our web sites design, improve our content, our services and usability. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the web site, new Services, and special offers. We always use a secure connection when collecting personal financial information from you. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Your ShipRocket account is password-protected and you are free to create further users and user groups to whom you shall assign Usernames and Passwords, so only you and those you designate can access it and view the member information relevant to your account. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. ShipRocket reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
